greenfaucet.com 2013-06-08

# Privacy Policy | Green Faucet

_**Green Faucet values your privacy and our Privacy Policy employs the “best practices” found on other major financial web sites of which you may already be a member.**_  This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Green Faucet and Green Faucet (http://www.greenfaucet.com) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the Green Faucet website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Green Faucet.

#### Personal Identification Information:

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

#### Non-personal Identification Information:

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

#### Web Browser Cookies:

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

#### Advertising:

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.  
How we use collected information:

Green Faucet collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To personalize user experience_  – We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _To improve our Site_  – We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * _To improve customer service_  – Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * _To process transactions_  – We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * _To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other Site feature_  – To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * _To send periodic emails  _– The email address Users provide for order processing, will be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions and for emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may[contact](mailto:info@greenfaucet.com) us via email. Green Faucet will periodically send out paid advertisements from third party vendors via email for the benefit of our subscribers. Although we have sent you these emails, Green Faucet does not endorse these products nor is it responsible for the content of these ads. Furthermore, we make no guarantee or warranty about what is advertised in these emails. Your privacy is very important to us. If you wish to be excluded from future notices, please [contact](mailto:info@greenfaucet.com) us via email. Green Faucet has not determined if the statements and opinions of the advertiser are accurate, correct or truthful. The purpose of these advertisements, like any advertising, is to provide publicity for the advertising company, its products or services. You should not rely on the information presented; you should do independent research to form your own opinion and decision. Information contained in our disseminated emails does not constitute investment, legal or tax advice upon which you should rely.

#### How we protect your information:

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.  
Sharing your personal information:

We share demographic, profile and other general information about you and our other customers with our advertisers on an aggregate basis. This means that we tell our advertisers general information about the characteristics of our customer base (e.g. geographical).

Our advertisers may ask us to mail or e-mail you promotional information tailored to your interests. We will send you this information on behalf of our advertisers. From time to time we may use third parties (pursuant to a confidentiality agreement) to assist us in e-mail broadcasts and list management. You may opt-out of receiving these mailings as explained below under the heading “Your Options.”

We may release your [contact](mailto:info@greenfaucet.com) and other information to third parties when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) cooperate with state and federal regulatory agency investigations, (iii) enforce the terms of our User Agreement or License Agreement, or (v) protect the rights of Green Faucet or others.

#### Third Party Websites:

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

#### Security:

Our Web site has certain security measures in place in effort to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

#### Compliance with Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

#### Your Options:

Opting to not receive promotional materials from our advertisers or messages from Green Faucet:

  * You may opt-out during the registration process or after registering by [contacting](mailto:info@greenfaucet.com) us via email.
  * Every e-mail we send to you will provide you with instructions on how to unsubscribe so that you will not receive any future e-mail.

#### Correct or Update Your Information:

You may correct or update any information previously provided to us by [contacting](mailto:info@greenfaucet.com) us via email.

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy:

Green Faucet has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

#### Your Acceptance of These Terms:

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

#### Contacting Us:

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please Green Faucet an email at info(at)greenfaucet(dot)com.

_This document was last updated on October 10, 2012._
